Soutar, Douglas H. Papers 5914
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Douglas H. Soutar Papers
1947-1992
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Soutar, Douglas H.
5914
30.5 cubic feet
30.5 linear ft.
Papers (documents).
5734517
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, July 23, 2013
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, April 17, 2019
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5914: Douglas H. Soutar Papers 5914 MB: Douglas H. Soutar Framed Feinsinger Memorial Statement Memorabilia 5914 P: Douglas H. Soutar Photograph
Soutar, Douglas H.; Day, Virgil B.; Petrie, James S.; Robinson, Drek; Rosow, Jerry
5734517
- Bargaining Material (Notebooks, transcripts of telephone conversations; NaCor material). (Box 1)
  - Steelworker Strike- Proposed Chicago Meeting+ Asarco Retroactivity Application- Splinter Groups, 1962-1967 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Revere Strike Postal Reform New Jersey Strike, Occupational Safety and Health Law, Miners and Mills USW Negotiations, 1963-1967 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Relocation and Retraining, Glover Negotiations, Buchans, 1963-1973 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - APPTS I 7-27-79 to 3-24-80, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Tel notes some Asarco Some Bus R; Govt. Appts, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - D Soutar, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - APPTS 11-6-80 to, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - 4-6-77 (NLRB) etc. Also some C-B, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - DH Sovtar C-B, NLRB, APPTS, etc., 1975 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Scope and Contents
    June-Aug. 25 '75
  - NLRB Apr 23-71 to, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - NLRB Apr 1971 to (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - July 15, 1959 to Aug. 7-1959 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - 11-23-53 to 2-1-54 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - August 7, 1959 to August 29,1959 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - 6-25-56 to 8-20-56, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - 12-18-56 to 1-21-57, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - April 30 '57 to June 25 '57, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - April 8-58 to 9-23-58, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - 1-23-57 to 4-30-57, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - June 25, '57 to Nov.7 '57, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - 10-18-54 to 5-2-54, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - 8-23-54 to 10-18-54 Including mm meetings in S. Lake 9-28-54 thru 9-30-54, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - 6-3-54 to 8-23-54 (mm notes Salt L SF), 1954 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - 8-20-56 to 9-20-56, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - 9-24-56 to 11-1-56, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - 12-5-58 to Feb 4,1959, 1958-1959 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Feb 3 1959 to March 13,1959 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - March 16, 1959 to Apr 1, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - April 1, 1959 to April 24, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - April 25,1959 to May 12, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - May 12, 1959 to June 9,1959 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - June 10,1959 to July 15,1959 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Nov.8 '57 to Arp. 3 '58, 1957-1958 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - 9-16-53 to 11-23-53, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - 8-14-53 to 9-16-53, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - 5-2-55 to 8-1-55, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - 4-18-56 to 6-22-56, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - 9-30-58 to 12-5-58, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - 10/22/52- 2/8/53, 1952-1953 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - MM H+W- 9-30-54 10-14-54 Garfield 10-5-54, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - 10-14-55 to 4-3-56, 1955-1956 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - 4-3-53 to 8-14-53, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - 2-8(9)-53 to 4-3-53, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - 2-1-54 to 6-3-54, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - 8-2-55 to 10-14-55, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - 11-1-56 to 12-18-56, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - ASARCO Council July 11 '60 S.F., 1960 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - 8/4/52-10/22/52, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - 2-11-52 to 8-4-52, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - MGRS Meeting 6-9-52 (N.4.), 1952 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - 9-5-51 to 2-7-52, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 51)
- Bargaining Material (phone conversations; NaCor material). (Box 2)
  - Granduc-M. Upham, 1966-1969 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - El Paso Wildcat Strike, Alton Negotiations, Coeur d ' Alenes Negotiations, Amarillo Labor, NWM Negotiations, 1963-1965 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - AIME Reception and Dinner, IRS, Letters, 1963-1964 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Kieffer's Letter, John R. Corbett Telephone Conversation
  - Hanover, New Mexico, Mine Kennecott Negotiations, Page- Galena Negotiations-Mine Mill, Whiting Wildcat, 1963-1968 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - RE: Glover, East Helena, Air Pollution Hearings, Carlsbad Bargaining, Re: Wage Reopener for J-M Canadian Asbestos Operations, INCO Settlement, 1966- 1968 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Baltimore-Sitdown Strike in Tank Hous, RE: San Francisco Wildcat, Assistant(s) for K.W. Nelson, Wildcat at Lake Asbestos, 1966-1969 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Kitchel, Bradley Pezzati, Shinkoskey Wes Foss Woodlief Horskyetc, 1958-1959 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Greenberg, Buck, Shantz Amarillo Steelworker Negotiations, Seniority, Reed, Smith, Brown etc., 1957-1958 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Trogdon, Waterman, MacKenzie, Moore, Messel, Bronstetter, Kieffer, Schwab, Shantz etc., 1955-1957 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Tittmann, Strole, Toomey, Doerr, Roy, Glueck, Feller, Campbell Arbitration etc., 1953-1955 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Mission Negotiations, Corpus Christi Negotiations, Silver Bell Negotiations, Galena Steelworker Petition To NLRB On Election, Operating Engineers Bargaining, Hayden Strike etc., 1962 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Schmertz, Auburn, Smith, Norman, Anderson, Lewis, Snedden, Kitchel, Cherouny, etc., 1962 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Roy, Hite, Lane, Corbett, Youtz, Teats, Shinkoskey, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Shinkoskey, Morrissey, Dichter, 1961-1962 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Granberg, Shinkoskey, Auburn, Dichter, Kieffer, Skow, Lane, Woodlief, Parkinson, 1960-1961 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Telephone Conversation between L. Buck and D. Soutar, Telephone Conversation with Koteen + August 20, 1953-1956 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    Tittmann, Jeffrey, Goldberg
  - McConigle, Bill Uren (Personal), Auburn, Reed, Dichter, Warren, Gordon, Bryant, Woodlief, 1959-1960 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Coeur d' Alene Strike, USW Negotiations & New Furnace, Woodlief, Hennebach, Montague, Dichter, Skinner, 1959-1961 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Coeur d' Alene Negotiations, Woodlief, Sievwright, Dalby, Wilson, Tittmann, Doerr&; Rouillard, Kieffer, 1956-1962 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - October 15, 1959 to November 5, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Sept 17,1959 to October 15,1959 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - February 2, 1960-July 27,1960 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - August 28, 1959 to Sept. 17, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Salaries (Personal), 1961-1962 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    Chapman, Uren, Monroe, Cherouny, McGregor, Dahm, Bowswell
  - Salaries, National Self-Insurers Association, J.C. Kieffer Phone Conversation, Salaries, 1961-1963 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    Gordon, Woodlief, Larson, Dichter, Michaelson, Parkinson, Skinner
  - Re Mission- Op Eng's Petition, Re: Hayden, Asbestos Negotiations, 1962-64 Settlement, RE: Mexican Labor, 1959-1962 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    Dichter, Gordon,
  - Re: Mission-op Eng's Petition, Re: Hayden, Asbestos Negotiations, RE: 1962-64 Settlement, 1960-1962 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    Dichter, Milliken, Snedden, WG Rouillard, Uren, Hite, Kohn, Gordon, Kleff, Larson, Flynn, Erickson
  - Baltimore Labor, Memorandum for Mr. Soutar: New Jersey Workmen's Compensation Proceedings, Inco, 1957-1963 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    Larson, Gordon, Dichter, Beckstead, Brown, Michaelson, Kleff
  - ASARCO- Memorandum for Mr. D. H. Soutar, Economic Progress and Economic Dislocation, 1980-1984 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - H.R. 2847, Shutdowns and Job Loss in California: The Need for New National Priorities, Application for Recognition of Exemption for the National Center on Occupational Readjustment, Inc., 1983 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Displacement Corporation of America, Key Plant Closing Statistics, Displacement Corp. of America to Advise Business on Plant Closings and Mass Layoffs, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    Pictures (5)
  - Findings: A Report on the Plant Closings Survey Conducted By NAM's Plant Closing Task Form Labor Relations Committee, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - To: Members, Employee Benefits Committee ACF Industries, BNA's Daily Reporter System, Richard P. Swigart, 1983-1984 (Box 2, Folder 32)
- Bargaining Material (NaCor & Video - Inst. of Collective Bargaining-Ted Kheel-Cornell). (Box 3)
  - NaCOR- Proposal for a Pilot/ Demonstration Project to Provide Occupational Readjustment Assistance to Employers and Employees Experiencing Permanent Business Closings, 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Working Paper Alfred P. Sloan School of Management- Major Employment Dislocation, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - NaCOR Plant Closings and Mass Layoffs: Lessons from Experience, 1982-1983 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    Revised Work Statement, Proposal for a Pilot/ Demonstration Project to Provide Occupational Readjustment Assistance to Employers and Employees Experiencing Permanent Business Closings
  - NaCOR- NaCOR List, 1982-1983 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    ASARCO, Articles of Incorporation of National Center on Occupational Readjustment
  - 2-26-62 to 3-5-62, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - End of Denver, Council Nepats to February 2, 1960, 1959-1960 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - 7-14-64 to 2-4-65 (includes Mission Jan Feb), 1964-1966 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - 2-4-65 to (starts with mission) Review for Mission sub, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - ILR Cornell Long-Term Incentive Compensation Plans Among the Top 200, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - November 6, 1959 to December 6,, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Feb 28 1964 to 7-14-64 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - July 29,1960 To, 1960-1961 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Cleary, Soutar, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - United States National Branch International Society for Labor Law and Social Security + United States Steel Corporation, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Business Closings and Worker Readjustment The Canadian Approach, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    David G. Newman, Esq. William Gardner, Esq.
  - NaCOR Trip 7-16-86, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - NaCOR-Strikes, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - NaCOR Clips, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - NaCOR, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - NaCOR-Funding, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - BRT-CC (Folder 1 of 3), 1977-1983 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - DHS- 1976 Christmas Card List BRT-CC (Folder 3 of 3) (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Institute of Collective Bargaining and Group Relations, Inc. ASARCO, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    Miscellaneous- The Big 50 Reunion of the 1935 Class of Sacramento High School May 11, 1985
  - ASARCO- File Memorandum+ The Historical Society of the Town of Greenwich Newsletter, 1983-1987 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - ILO, 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - United States Council for International Business- Memorandum: Manpower and Social Affairs Committee Structural Employment Policies, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Newmont Service Limited Collective Bargaining Problems of the American Copper Industry: A Report to Newmont Mining Corporation, 1984-1985 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - George Hildebrand- Collective Bargaining Problems of the American Copper Industry: A Report to Newmont Mining Corporation, New York Chapter- Industrial Relation Research Assoc., 1977-1986 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Christmas Card List 1978-1979 Australian Mines and Metals Association, 1978-1984 (Box 3, Folder 29)
- Soutar Speechs. (Box 4)
  - NaCOR National Center on Occupational Readjustment, Inc. Financial Statements, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - NaCOR DHS cc Lovell JBJ's, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    -Statement of Malcolm R. Lovell, JR. Chairman, Secretary of Labor's Task Force on Economic Adjustment and Worker Dislocation Before the Subcommittee on Employment and Productivity Committee on Labor and Human Resources United States Senate -Testimony o
  - NaCOR Business Closings and Worker Readjustment The Canadian Approach, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - NaCOR- Memorandum D. Soutar, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - NaCOR Strategy for U.S. Industrial Competitiveness- A statement by the Research and Policy Committee of the Committee for Economic Development, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Footnotes to the Policy Statement Strategy for U.S. Industrial Competitiveness (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Carnegie-Mellon University + proceedings of the First Annual Labor Relations Conference, 1982-1983 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - NaCOR Annual Report, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Letters (Wollstadt, Raskin, Larson, Oakes, Douglas Soutar ) INCO Negotiations and Strike, 1957-1983 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - The Business Roundtable Construction Committee, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - United States Council for International Business- Doug Soutar, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - United States Delegation Report, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Testimony of J. Bruce Johnston on Behalf of the National Association of Manufacturers Dislocation: Who, What, Where, When+ Administration's Proposal, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Regulating Plant Closings and Mass Layoffs: A Summary of Foreign Requirements, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Economic Adjustment and Worker Dislocation in a Competitive Society, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    Report of the Secretary of Labor's Task Force on Economic Adjustment and Worker Dislocation
  - NaCOR- Board of Trustees D.H. Soutar Meeting May 7 '84, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - National Center on Occupational Readjustment, Inc. Third Meeting of the Board of Trustees, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Copper Strike, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Copper Strike Information Bureau, 1967-1986 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Clearinghouse- Legislative Status & Analysis Report, Statement of the National Center for Occupational Readjustment, 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - The Next American Revolution: Crisis in Employment, H.R. 1122(DHS'cc) Clearinghouse- Legislative Status and Analysis Report, Special Report, Update, 1985- 1987 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Clearinghouse- Vol. 1 No.1, Vol.2 No. 16, Vol. III No.1, 2,3 and Special Alert, 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Current Developments, NACOR Board Meeting, Opening Statement William L. Clay, Why Plants Close, 1985-1987 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - National Association of Manufacturers: Testimony of John S. Irving, JR. United States Conference of Mayors: Statement by the Honorable Angelo Martinelli Mayor of Yonkers, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Newspaper Clippings- New York Times (Folder 1 of 4), 1985 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Newspaper Clippings New York Times (Folder 1 of 5), 1985 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Newspaper Clippings (Folder 2 of 4), 1988 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Newspaper Clippings (Folder 2 of 5), 1988 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Newspaper Clippings (Folder 3 of 4), 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    Most articles relate to Stocks, bonds
  - Newspaper Clippings (Folder 3 of 5), 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Newspaper Clippings (Folder 4 of 5), 1986 (Box 4, Folder 28)
    Some articles relate to economics
  - Newspaper Clippings(Folder 5 of 5), 1986 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Brochures(A guide to the University Club Library, The Newcomen Bulletin for the United States, Labor and Employment Law in the United States, Attendance List, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - American Arbitration Association Industrial Relations Research Association Series Newsletter, Arbitration Day '87, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - An Overview of Labor Management Relations in 1983: Douglas H. Soutar (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Preempting Governmental Regulation of the Work Place through Self-Enlightened Policy Planning (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Coming to Grips with Some Major Problems in the Construction Industry (2) and The Business Roundtable Brochures (5), 1978-1982 (Box 4, Folder 34)
- Construction Roundtable (Mainly 1980's; Construction Committee Roundtable). (Box 5)
  - BR-cc (Folder 1 of 2), 1986-1987 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - BR-cc Future (Folder 2 of 2), 1981-1986 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Construction Comm.- more recent- minutes (Folder 1 of 5), 1980-1982 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Construction comm.- more recent- minutes (Folder 2 of 5), 1980-1983 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    BR Construction Committee
  - Construction comm.- more recent- minutes (Folder 3 of 5), 1983 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    Business Roundtable Construction Committee
  - Construction comm.- more recent- minutes Business Closings and Worker Readjustment (Folder 4 of 5), 1987 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Construction comm.- more recent- minutes (Folder 5 of 5), 1981-1983 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    ASARCO
  - Construction Comm.- more recent.- General (Folder 1 of 5), 1981-1983 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    The Business Roundtable
  - Construction comm.- more recent- General (Folder 2 of 5), 1982-1984 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    The Business Roundtable Construction Committee
  - Construction comm.- more recent- General (Folder 3 of 5), 1980-1983 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Construction comm.- more recent- General (Folder 4 of 5), 1974-1983 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Construction comm.- more recent- General (Folder 5 of 5), 1982 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Brochures ( The Consumption Tax: A Better Alternative?, Labor Management Cooperation, EEO, Industry and Labor), 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    Misc.- Gibson, Dunn & Crutcher Announcement
  - Occupational Safety and Health Review Commission, ILR Cornell, 1981-1986 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - A.T. Flynn, 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - NaCOR Industrial Relations Research Association, 1964-1973 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Creative Bargaining- Does It Make Sense As a Future Policy (Folder 1 of 2), 1984 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Creative Bargaining- Does It Make Sense As a Future Policy (Folder 2 of 2), 1984 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - An Era of Challenge for Collective Bargaining and New York Chapter Industrial Relations Research Association, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Changing Nature of Employee Relations and National Industrial Policy, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Legislative and Regulatory Update, Statement by Thomas R. Donahue, Secretary Treasurer, New York Times Article, 1986-1987 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - D.H Soutar Nov.10-75, Feb.5 -76, 1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Twenty Questions & Answers on Comparable Worth, Plant Closings, Remarks of E.B. Miller At Luncheon For Frank McCulloch, Sept.11, 1970, 1970- 1983 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Plant Closings- Worker Rights, Management Rights and the Law For the Labor Management Professional, 1983-1987 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - BR- Construction Users Anti-Inflation Roundtable Membership, 1969-1973 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - BR Construction Users Anti-Inflation Roundtable 1969-1970 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Public Information Committee The Corporate Lobbies: Political Profiles of the Business The Roundtable Chamber of Commerce, 1972-1973 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - BR- Task Force on Scheduled Overtime, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 28)
- Business Rountable (plus one file re multi-employer bargaining-possibly NLRB early 1970's). (Box 6)
  - BR - Policy Re: Broadening Area- Collective Bargaining in Construction, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Construction- Office of Construction in Department of Commerce, 1974-1976 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - BR- Contractors Mutual Assn. Wage Guidelines-The Negative Impact Upon Construction, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Construction- Productivity, 1977-1978 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Construction- National Constructors Association, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Construction- No- Strike Agreement, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Construction- National Conference on Construction Problems- US CofC, 1968-1969 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Restructuring of Bargaining in Construction Industry, 1972-1977 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - BR- Construction Committee Meetings- 1978, 1978-1979 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Construction - Intra-Company Construction Councils, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Construction - Industry Improvement Funds, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Construction- Job Classification, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - BR- Construction - Multi-Employer Bargaining (Folder 1 of 2), 1970-1972 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - BR- Construction-Multi-Employer Bargaining (Folder 2 of 2), 1970-1973 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - BR- Construction Comm. - Task Force on Productivity, 1977-1978 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - BR- Construction Users Anti- Inflation Roundtable 1971-1972 (Folder 1 of 2) (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - BR- Construction Users Anti-Inflation Roundtable 1971-1972 (Folder 2 of 2) (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - BR Construction Committee (Folder 1 of 7 ), 1969-1980 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - BR Construction Committee (Folder 2 of 7), 1980 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - BR Construction Committee (Folder 3 of 7), 1979 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - BR Construction Committee (Folder 4 of 7), 1975-1977 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - BR Construction Committee (Folder 5 of 7), 1977-1979 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - BR Construction Committee (Folder 6 of 7), 1975-1978 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - BR Construction Committee (Folder 7 of 7), 1977-1980 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - BR - Troika, 1970-1973 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - LLRS/LLSG- Press Releases, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Business Roundtable Annual Mtg DS Report 6/16/75, 1973-1975 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - LLR Letter to Senators, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 28)
- NLRB (some NLRB; "Troika"; Labor Law Reform late 1970's; Labor Law Study Group). (Box 7)
  - BR Post- Murphy (Folder 1 of 2), 1971-1973 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - BR Murphy Post (Folder 2 of 2), 1971-1973 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Blue Ribbon Panel (Lawyers) - BRT, 1968-1972 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - BR Membership Structure, Committees, Changes in Membership, Interested Applicants, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Labor Law Reform, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - LLSC- NLRB, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - LLSC Progress Reports Internal, 1966-1970 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - DS Speech Business Roundtable- AMC 1966 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - BR- Telex's & Mailgrams Sent, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Business Roundtable: General, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - BR Old (Folder 1 of 5), 1973 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - BR Old (Folder 2 of 5), 1971-1973 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - BR Old (Folder 3 of 5), 1973 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - BR Old BR Post-Murphy: Dirksen (Folder 4 of 5), 1965 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - BR Old DS 3-29-72 RE "Business Action Council" (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - LLRS/ LLSG - Steering Committee, 1969-1972 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - LMC Annual Meeting 6-17-74, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    Clippings 6-17, 6-17-80
  - BR- LLSG - Public Education Program, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - BR- Old, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - LLRS/ LLSG- Membership, 1967-1970 (Box 7, Folder 20)
- LLRS/LLSG- Mission, 1970-1973 (Box 7a, Folder 1)
- LLRS/LLSG- Expenses, 1971 (Box 7a, Folder 2)
- LLSC- General, 1970-1975 (Box 7a, Folder 3)
- LLRS/ LLSG - Conference on Labor Policy- Sept/Oct 1971 (Box 7a, Folder 4)
- LLRS/LLSG- Labor Law Relations Film, 1969 (Box 7a, Folder 5)
- LLSG - Carol Hageman Interview 1972, 1970-1972 (Box 7a, Folder 6)
- LLRS/LLSG- Lobbying, 1971 (Box 7a, Folder 7)
- Blue Ribbon Committee (Labor Law Study Group & old Blue Ribbon Committee). (Box 8)
  - LLRS/LLSG- Hilbert Memo & Day Speech, 1967-1972 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - BR Old (Folder 1 of 6), 1968-1974 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - BR Old - Welfare- Food Stamps (Folder 2 of 6), 1975 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - BR Old (Folder 3 of 6), 1969-1973 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - BR Old (Folder 4 of 6), 1971-1974 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - BR Old (Folder 5 of 6), 1969-1973 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - BR Old (Folder 6 of 6), 1966-1970 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - LLSC Steering Committee (Folder 1 of 3), 1969-1973 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - BR GSA Mtg. and Labor-Management Committee (Folder 2 of 3), 1971-1974 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Labor Law Study Group (Folder 3 of 3), 1968-1971 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Tudor Dinner- Business Roundtable, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - BR- Hageman Dinner, 1873 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - BR- Retirement Dinner for Denise- Hendrix- Duemler, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - LLRS/LLSG - Taft- Hartley, 1965-1969 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - LLRS/LLSG - Meetings, 1970-1977 (Box 8, Folder 15)